[Respect Copyright, Everyone's Responsibility]
[The Eternal Fragrance]
[Adapted from Shisilang's novel, The Eternal Fragrance]
[Episode 15]
Demonic energy?
Lei.
How did you get hurt so badly?
Let me see.
Don't bother.
Don't refuse, Lei.
Your wound has a grass spirit in it.
It'll be hard to stop the bleeding.
I'll go back to Yaoguang Peak and tend to it myself.
By the way,
Please take
This Vermilion Fruit to Baicao Peak.
Lei, don't worry.
I'll make sure it gets there.
You're finally awake.
Master, Mr. Dongyang.
Looks like that Vermilion Fruit really works.
It does.
We can rest easy now.
Lei has already gone back.
Lifei, are you feeling any better?
Lifei, you owe Qin this time.
If he hadn't gathered that Vermilion Fruit,
You'd be in serious trouble.
Lifei's medicine should be ready. I'll go check on it.
There's something we need to ask you.
You must tell us the truth.
This is important. Don't hide anything.
Was I also tainted by demonic energy,
Like Songfeng?
Lei.
Today, Master asked where you'd been.
I told him you were in seclusion training.
You were in such a hurry last night.
Was it something urgent?
Nothing. Thanks for asking.
If you don't want to say, that's fine.
This healing salve can stop bleeding and draw out poison.
Cailing, how did you know?
There's a lot you don't know.
If there's a chance, I'll tell you everything.
A wound like this, from a spirit creature,
Needs Elder Dongyang's medicine to heal.
From what Lifei said, her former master
Was an expert
And
Had to go into hiding for some special reason.
Skilled in sealing techniques
And quite knowledgeable about talismans as well.
Alright.
After I find out which scumbag
Hurt Lifei,
I'll make a trip to Qingqiu myself.
Don't mention this to anyone
Until we know more.
Don't worry.
I brought Lifei to Wuyue Court.
I'll make sure she's safe.
Look at you.
I'm telling you,
Qin treats Lifei differently from everyone else.
Don't practice for the next few days.
Get some rest.
And don't worry about the kitchen.
Let them fast for a while.
I heard Lifei got through that
Because Qin brought her the Vermilion Fruit.
Lifei, Qin gives you treasures
And medicine.
You might have to marry him
To pay that back.
Simo, since you like Qin so much,
Why don't you take that honor?
Qin is a model disciple of Wuyue Court.
How can you joke about that?
The incense is lit, and the bed is made.
Let Lifei rest.
Was there really a demon spy back then?
What do demons even look like? Uglier than the ones in storybooks?
Who's there?
Darn it. Nightmare spell again.
Stay calm through all changes. Keep your spirit steady and your mind clear.
A heart that is clear like water, and the water is the heart.
Break!
Who are you?
What is Qingcheng to you?
Ouch, let go.
Don't be afraid.
Which peak are you from?
What technique did you just use?
Sir,
I'm from Zhuiyu Peak.
That was the Earth-Shattering Turtle Technique
My master taught me.
Turtle Technique?
It's Five Turtles Technique.
Then I misremembered.
That name is so hard to remember.
Wonder who came up with it.
That person is always reckless.
Why are you here so late at night?
Well,
My master sent me to Baicao Peak to pick up some medicine.
My cultivation is shallow.
With the wind and fog, I lost my way.
Sir,
I'm in a hurry.
I'll be going.
That man had a long beard and looked fierce!
He immediately asked me
What Qingcheng was to me.
His... His glare alone
Could have burned right through me.
From what you're saying,
That old man was probably my senior brother,
Cuixuan.
Elder Cuixuan?
I thought he was in seclusion.
Who's Qingcheng?
His enemy?
Don't talk about things you don't know.
Remember,
Don't use the Five Turtles Technique in front of outsiders.
And lately, none of you
Should go wandering around.
Master, could the one
Who attacked Lifei be connected
To that demon spy?
There are so many disciples in Wuyue Court.
Why target Lifei?
Yeah. Lifei's spirit energy is average,
And her cultivation is low. What's the spy after?
Is he blind?
Well, maybe
He sees me as Wuyue Court's rising star.
Then he's not just blind. He's also an idiot.
Alright. Let's focus on what matters.
Whoever it is, they easily
Broke through Zhuiyu Peak's restriction spell
And located Lifei's room.
That scumbag knows this place well.
Elder Chongyi!
Sir, Songfeng has woken up
And identified the demon spy.
My master has invited everyone to Wengu Hall for an interrogation.
Qin, who's the demon spy?
Lei Xiuyuan.
It's him!
The day before the incident, he practiced in front of me.
After he finished, he left the scroll on the training platform.
I picked it up and wanted to return it.
But out of curiosity, I flipped through it.
Turns out it was demonic arts!
Lei Xiuyuan, you plotted against me.
How vicious of you!
I hurriedly came out of seclusion
To find the demonic rot
Hidden within our sect.
Whether Lei Xiuyuan has done anything improper
Is a matter of our sect's safety.
You must speak everything you know.
Elder Cuixuan,
Lei Xiuyuan
Has repeatedly broken Zhuiyu Peak's restriction spell.
Master,
On the night Jiang Lifei had the accident at Yuelian Pond,
Lei was also there.
Seems a bit too coincidental.
It wasn't Lei Xiuyuan.
Lifei, you never saw that person.
How do you know it wasn't him?
Lei Xiuyuan did meet me in private a few times,
But he never meant me any harm.
My master opened my sea of mind.
If anyone had ill intent, I would've sensed it.
Songfeng,
You said
Lei Xiuyuan was practicing on the platform the night before the accident.
What time was it?
Around the Xu hour.
Are you sure?
Lifei, what are you trying to say?
Lei Xiuyuan couldn't have been at Yaoguang Peak during the Xu hour.
He didn't leave Zhuiyu Peak until the Mao hour.
Thick fog and long roads lie between the two peaks.
Even with his cultivation,
It takes four hours to go back and forth.
So by the time he got to Yaoguang Peak,
The Xu hour would've long passed.
Am I right?
Yes.
I don't remember clearly!
Besides, that's just your one-sided story.
Maybe you have some old ties with Lei Xiuyuan
And are covering for him.
Zhaomin can testify.
Zhaomin,
You saw him that day, too, didn't you?
Songfeng, I know you lost to Lei,
But win or lose, it's the way of things.
Don't take it too much to heart.
You wretch! Are you falsely accusing him
Out of jealousy and spite?
I'm not! It's Lei Xiuyuan!
He broke through the third level in just three days.
He must've been secretly practicing demonic arts!
Metal Spirit Root? Gifted?
He's probably the demon spy!
True or not, I'll find out with one test.
Zuo Qiu's seal?
Mr. Zuo?
If Lei Xiuyuan were of demon kind,
He would never have made it out of the Danxue secret realm.
Cuixuan, let's leave it here.
Cuixuan, he's someone Mr. Zuo Qiu protects.
He's probably fine.
We need to focus on finding the real demon spy.
Otherwise, more disciples will get hurt.
That could become a serious problem.
Alright. You may go.
As for the one who falsely accused a fellow disciple,
He will have his cultivation stripped and be expelled.
Master. Master.
Have mercy, please.
Master.
Master, have mercy!
I was wrong.
I propose we move next year's Achillea Bead Tournament
Up to next month.
First,
It will help us identify talents to face the Sea Calamity.
Second,
It will let us probe the disciples
And root out the demon spy.
Any objections?
What's the Achillea Bead?
It's a heavenly treasure Elder Cuixuan found
In an ancient secret realm 300 years ago.
It was formed from a thousand-year-old achillea plant.
They say its spirit energy is incredible. It strengthens spirit meridians
And boosts cultivation.
So what's the Achillea Bead Tournament?
Elder Cuixuan holds a combat tournament
Every three years to encourage us to cultivate hard.
The winner can absorb the Achillea Bead's spirit power
To boost their cultivation
And also enter its illusion
To seek an answer
To the one question they most want to know.
It can talk?
No. It's more like a connection.
In ancient times, achillea was often used for divination.
A thousand-year-old achillea is said to understand the ways of heaven.
It's profound beyond words.
Like our master's turtle shell?
Since it's for divination,
I could ask it where Master is.
I said no, and that's final!
Don't bring this up again!
Master, I want to win the Achillea Bead Tournament.
Wouldn't that bring honor to Zhuiyu Peak?
Just give me a few magic treasures.
No need. Really, no.
We don't need you bringing honor to us!
Listen up,
Just go through the motions. That's all!
I think it's worth a shot.
Nonsense!
Master!
Just stay alive.
I...
Food and drink are what matter most!
- But I... - Enough!
No, wait.
- Go away. - Ma...
Master!
Winning is a good thing, isn't it?
Why are you leaving?
Why did Master rush off like that?
Did you make him angry again?
No, I didn't.
I just told him
I wanted to win the Achillea Bead Tournament.
Then he blew up.
Master means well.
This tournament is said to be for selecting vanguard fighters
To face the Sea Calamity.
Sea Calamity?
That great disaster
That comes every 500 years?
It's more than a disaster. It's an apocalypse.
Five hundred years ago, the Sea Calamity struck.
Giant waves flooded Guixu.
Demons across the seas invaded and slaughtered countless lives.
The immortal sects of the Central Plains were destroyed.
Wuyue Court was nearly wiped out as well.
Elder Cuixuan and Elder Guangwei were badly wounded.
They spent centuries recovering.
Our master barely survived.
So he's wary of that apocalypse
And treats it like a threat.
No wonder Master reacted so strongly.
But if the Sea Calamity really comes,
As cultivators, we can't escape it.
We'll have to face it anyway.
That's not for you to worry about.
The spy trying to harm you hasn't been caught yet.
Just
Focus on your training at Zhuiyu Peak.
Jiang.
This is essence-nurturing water my master made.
It regulates your breath and strengthens your vital energy.
It'll also help you recover.
Thanks, Qin.
You found me the Vermilion Fruit
And gave me this magic medicine.
If there's ever anything I can do for you,
Just say the word.
Actually,
The first time I saw you at the academy,
You left a deep impression on me.
I'm really glad you came to Wuyue Court.
Lifei, I...
I'm really happy, too.
Qin,
You're kind and experienced.
Do you know any way to win
The Achillea Bead Tournament?
You want to win?
Then I'll help you.
Really?
Come on, let's talk it through.
You're not fully healed,
Yet you insist on entering the tournament.
Is it for Jiang Lifei?
Yes.
The one who harmed her hasn't been found.
I can't rest easy.
Do you know about the Sea Calamity?
Five hundred years ago,
My master, the sect leader of Wuyue Court,
And so many fellow disciples
Sacrificed their lives to hold the East Sea
And protect the Central Plains.
Now, as the leading immortal sect,
Wuyue Court will once again be at the forefront against the Sea Calamity.
By then, you, as one of our finest disciples,
Will stand with me against the demons.
You have Jiaping's talent
And a stronger will than his.
You are a genius of a generation.
Don't let an obsession with love cloud your duty to the greater good.
Are you really entering the tournament?
For Jiang Lifei,
You almost got branded a demon spy.
Are you planning
To die for her next time?
None of your concern.
You...
Jiang Lifei.
Mr. Dongyang, what are you doing?
You'll know
When the tournament comes.
You're mostly healed.
But your heart meridians are damaged.
To fully recover,
You'll need another Vermilion Fruit.
Elder Dongyang.
Sir, I'm here to pick up medicine for Lei.
I'll get it.
Thank you.
Yue.
What... what happened to Lei Xiuyuan?
Was he hurt by Songfeng?
Lifei, you're so innocent and charming.
You bewitch without even trying.
Why pretend you don't know?
Two bottles for external use. One for internal.
Since it's a spirit creature wound,
Don't let it get wet.
And he shouldn't circulate his energy or practice these next few days.
Otherwise, the wound will worsen,
And the pain will be unbearable.
I'll keep it all in mind. Thank you.
Wounded by a spirit creature?
Sir,
Was the Vermilion Fruit I took
Gathered by Lei Xiuyuan?
Since you don't care about him,
Leave Lei alone
And let him focus on his cultivation.
Or it would hurt both of you.
I thought Qin saved me?
I'm not sure of the details.
Maybe they both wanted to save you.
But Lei was the one who dove in to get the fruit.
Tongzhou?
I'm fine.
Take care of yourself at Xingzheng Hall.
I'll come see you when I have time.
Your Highness, Her Highness is here again.
Tongzhou.
Sit.
Have Mingli show you around in a bit.
I've been busy lately.
Tongzhou, I don't need anyone to accompany me.
Just let me stay by your side.
Mr. Xuanshan has me in seclusion for training. You can't follow.
Besides, it's improper for us to be alone together.
Then let's just get married.
Once we're married,
No one will have anything to say.
Lanya, I've told you many times.
We're cousins. I won't marry you.
But His Majesty said
Our engagement would go ahead as planned.
Lanya, I can give you anything else.
Just not this.
I have to go see Mr. Xuanshan soon.
Sit here for a while.
Tongzhou.
Deities above.
I know
I'll never see him again in this life.
But I can't stop thinking about him every day.
Even though he's probably forgotten me,
I'm willing to trade my years
For the prince's happiness and safety.
Duantu?
Are you telling me to go find him at Duantu?
Thank you so much.
Qin.
Longyuan Manifestation?
Lei,
You haven't even been here a year,
Yet you've already mastered such fierce sword arts.
Where there are people, there are conflicts.
Without the ability to protect yourself,
You're bound to be set up.
Lei, you misunderstand.
But you were there both when Lifei was attacked
And when Songfeng fell into demonhood.
I'm just worried you might've been tainted by demonic energy.
Just being cautious.
If you suspect me,
You can just report it to Elder Cuixuan.
I'll see it through and get to the truth.
And
When I find the one who harmed Lifei,
Regardless of who it is,
I won't let them off.
♪I trade all the mortal world's splendor♪
♪For a fleeting moment with you♪
♪Our fates intertwined, embracing yet fighting♪
♪The hardest bond to balance♪
♪Obsessed and struggling, a thousand thoughts arise♪
♪Love sprouts again in this lifetime♪
♪No calamity can rival♪
♪The lingering thread of a fragrance♪
♪With you, through mountains falling and seas turning to sand♪
♪Withered branches burst into bloom♪
♪Hand in hand on the Naihe Bridge. Past the pagoda♪
♪In fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still♪
♪Reign supreme♪
♪With you, we melt into mist and haze♪
♪Deep love and long yearning, a kiss falls into a dream♪
♪In the distant night, bitterness blooms♪
♪The grand chapter is rewritten♪
♪Startling the whole world♪
Don't let the wound get wet.
And he shouldn't circulate his energy or practice these next few days.
Otherwise, the wound will worsen,
And the pain will be unbearable.
♪In fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still♪
♪Reign supreme♪
♪If the seal can't be broken, then let it go♪
♪Where the heart finds peace, there is home♪
♪Side by side, we fly through seas of clouds. Break through the waves♪
♪The heart's ocean knows no shore♪
♪Always, at the very end of fate♪
♪Comes that one moment of defiance♪
♪In the human world or above, like flowing water♪
♪And falling petals♪
♪Let this fleeting life be whatever it may♪
The Achillea Bead Tournament will span three days.
May all disciples from every peak give their full effort.
Prepare yourselves for the coming Sea Calamity.
All disciples from the sixteen peaks must participate.
By the end of the Wu hour,
Sixteen winners will advance to the second round.
From the Wei hour onward, the top eight will be decided.
To ensure each peak has a disciple in the second round,
Zhuiyu Peak gets a bye in the first round.
- Really? - That's great!
Cuixuan, isn't that unfair?
Baifu, have you lost your mind?
Under Cuixuan's leadership, Wuyue Court
Has never been unfair.
How could it be unfair?
We're about to start. Stop your nonsense.
Shut your mouth.
Let the tournament begin!
Amazing.
As expected of Qin.
Incredible.
Lifei, hurry.
Lei has already won six matches.
Everyone says it's spectacular.
If we're late, we'll miss the best parts.
Lei is really impressive.
- As expected of Lei. - Yeah.
Absolutely amazing.
Lei is incredible!
Were you two really fellow disciples?
What are you implying?
Nothing. Just that
Talent levels differ, and quality varies.
You...
Lifei.
The name tag for your second-round opponent is out.
Who am I facing?
Deng Xiguang.
Deng?
That's Elder Baifu's top disciple.
Deng Xiguang?
It's okay, Lifei.
Just going through the motions.
Remember my name! I'm Deng Xiguang!
I have an idea.
As the Sage taught,
Extend the respect and care
You show your own family to others as well.
As your senior,
I'll go easy on you
And let you lose with dignity.
Deng, you're such a good person.
Please accept my bow.
Lime powder?
Sorry, Deng.
I'm too busy training
To wash my clothes.
It's all dust. See?
See?
As the Sage taught,
Winning unfairly is dishonorable, but yielding shows...
Virtue!
Did he faint from shock?
- How did he faint? - He just fainted?
No way.
That's one way to do it.
Didn't see that coming.
I won!
Which peak is she from?
Yeah.
Is she from Zhuiyu Peak?
I don't know. I don't recognize her.
I don't know her!
Outrageous!
Can such a despicable win even count?
Baifu, watch your words.
What do you mean, despicable?
That's called strategy and quick thinking.
Magic is a contest of both power and strategy.
Don't you understand?
She truly has her master's style.
Yes. She's my disciple. What of it?
As expected of your disciple.
The top eight are set. Tomorrow will determine the top four.
Jiang Lifei versus Tang De.
Qin Yangling versus Cheng Feng.
Yue Cailing versus Ban Tou.
Lei Xiuyuan versus Wu Jiahui.
All participating disciples
Have taken enough demon-purging water.
Any who have secretly practiced demonic arts
Will lose control and be exposed tonight.
[The Eternal Fragrance]
[Adapted from Shisilang's novel, The Eternal Fragrance]
♪I trade all the mortal world's splendor♪
♪For a fleeting moment with you♪
♪Our fates intertwined, embracing yet fighting♪
♪The hardest bond to balance♪
♪Obsessed and struggling, a thousand thoughts arise♪
♪Love sprouts again in this lifetime♪
♪No calamity can rival the lingering thread of a fragrance♪
♪With you, through mountains falling and seas turning to sand♪
♪Withered branches burst into bloom♪
♪Hand in hand on the Naihe Bridge♪
♪Past the pagoda, in fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still reign supreme♪
♪With you, we melt into mist and haze♪
♪I trade the highest heaven and endless clouds♪
♪For a fleeting moment with you♪
♪Pierced by countless arrows, pain and illness pile on♪
♪Yet I remain silent♪
♪Deep love and long yearning, a kiss falls into a dream♪
♪In the distant night, bitterness blooms♪
♪The grand chapter is rewritten, startling the whole world♪
♪With you, through mountains falling and seas turning to sand♪
♪Withered branches burst into bloom♪
♪Hand in hand on the Naihe Bridge♪
♪Past the pagoda, in fine robes on galloping horses♪
♪Always, at the very end of obsession♪
♪Comes that one moment of softness♪
♪Betrayed by all, I still reign supreme♪
♪If the seal can't be broken, then let it go♪
♪Where the heart finds peace, there is home♪
♪Side by side, we fly through seas of clouds♪
♪Break through the waves; the heart's ocean knows no shore♪
♪Always, at the very end of fate♪
♪Comes that one moment of defiance♪
♪In the human world or above, like flowing water and falling petals♪
♪Let this fleeting life be whatever it may♪